Hey. Lenny! Open up the door. homie!
- Shit.
- Whoa. God!
- Hey. what we talking 'bout. man?
- Just a couple grand.
Couple grand. huh?
You take a gun out of this house.
you better be ready to use it.
They're decommissioned. They're
on their way to destruction.
No deal.
You have a problem
with the serial number.
Okay. before we go. you
and I. we get power tools.
we grind the numbers out ourselves.
www  .  OpenSubtitles  .  org
Tomás o Enrique?
Should be Enrique.
I told you. Enrique's a killer.
He's big. el vato.
I'll make sure the door's unlocked.
You two go in behind me.
- ¿Dónde?
- En una de las bolsas.
Right there.
What?
- Synced and corrected by javiernv -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hey! Don't shoot.
Found out where Karvel stay.
Word is. he been spending. too.
Nasty down here.
Smell like my cousin's mattress.
Oh. shit!
We go over there. hope
you do better than that.
What you need to do is
shoot something real.
Get the fuck outta here. man.
You can't kill nothing living.
then how you gonna kill Karvel?
You real enough. Want
me to shoot you. huh?
Hey. give me that shit.
- Don't want that booty bandit near me.
- Nah. man.
Hey. come on. square
ass. Let me get that shit.
Man. back up. fake-ass Tookie.
Hey. come on. let me
give it a shot. nigga.
- Let go...
- Shit!
Shoot. My bad. nigga.
It's a loaded fucking gun!
What the hell is wrong with you. man?!
You ain't gotta be
doing all that yelling!
You wanna be the trigger
man. go ahead. It's all you.
Just...
Um. hola.
¡Intruso!
Sh...
Amigo. amigo.
No. no! No!
Wait. Come on.
Hey. hey. uh...
¡Intruso! ¡Hay un intruso! ¡Oiganme.
alguien se ha infiltrado!
Estaba en centinela y lo
vi saliendo de la selva.
Uh. uh. uh. Paz. Paz. I-I come in Paz.
Quiero hablar con Alejandro Estévez.
Jesus Christ.
Morning.
How the fucking hell did you get here?
Are you wondering which
planes I took specifically
or what Podunk towns I took 'em to?
Or you're asking how I found
this well-hidden haven
of guerilla warfare?
Let's put it this way.
It's a good thing the Sandinistas
don't have access to the
same satellites as the CIA
So you came here for the rockets?
I told you. Those serial
numbers are coming off.
Well. I've got the FSLN
breathing down my neck.
I've got mines to set. coke to pack...
Then we should probably get started now.
Tell your men.
You have a leech on your bicep.
Oh. Oh. God. Ugh!
Thirsty?
I put one of those iodine tablets in it.
Has it been at least 30 minutes?
'Cause it takes at least 30 minutes
for the iodine to start
to kill off the pathogens.
- Just drink it.
- Thanks.
Mamamé la verga. gringo hijo de puta.
Mámatela tu mismo. Mateo.
¿Le gusta que se la mamen?
Por eso pierden la guerra.
Hey. who's that kid?
He belong to anyone?
Wandered into camp a while back.
Lived on a ranch nearby.
But his dad got sick and died.
Popeye. ven acá chaval.
Te vas a enfermar si sigues
comiendo ese chocolate.
Me gusta tu radio. ¿Funciona?
Yeah.
Where do you learn such
good Spanish. G.I. Joe?
Uh. university.
You wanna play some music?
Don't wanna waste battery.
Only station we get
here is news. anyway.
You a baseball fan?
Yeah. You?
Crazy kid.
Got any of your own?
No.
Shit. yeah. Jesus. what am I saying?
Um. I have a son.
You remember his name
or you forget that. too?
His name is Paul.
He is 2.
Guessing you don't get to see him much.
Yeah. Well. you know...
travel to tropical paradises
seems to keep me
otherwise occupied lately.
Mm.
Been circling for weeks.
Only a matter of time
before they find us.
You don't like him?
It isn't personal.
No. but you still don't like him.
He wasn't always so difficult.
You lose enough. it changes you.
Underneath it all. he
just wants his life back.
same as the rest of us.
Sounds like you know him pretty well.
Yeah. well...
He's my husband.
No. he didn't.
There's your money.
And those rims is 800 bucks apiece.
At least his punk ass
know how to get down.
- Sure he in here?
- I don't know.
Hey. hold up. You're ready
to smoke his ass. right?
'Cause if we take that
car. he gonna hunt us down
and rape our asses like
a couple of bitches. too.
Stay with me. man.
Nigga so turnt out. he turnt over.
Hey. what the fuck?
Puta madre.
How much longer we
have to wait?
Till dark.
Dark like...
like 7:30 or...
Midnight.
Midnight?
But it gets dark at like...
I don't like this kind.
The caramel.
Gets stuck in my teeth.
My hands are dirty.
We gotta
watch her. keep an eye.
Look at her. She's
not handling this well.
She takes spiders outside.
yells at me if I kill one.
Can't even handle spider
guts. How's she supposed to...
Do you think it was weird
Enrique had that poster on his wall?
¿Qué?
Yeah. it was near
where I found his hand.
when we were cleaning.
This guy's good.
I like the way he draws tits.
For some movie called "Prom Night."
"If you're not back by midnight.
you won't be coming home."
How bad is it?
I've seen worse.
You know what you're doing. right?
Why would Enrique have a
poster like that on his wall?
I don't seem him liking a
movie enough to buy the poster.
Maybe he found it?
Or somebody gave it to him.
- Aah!
- Perdona.
Sorry.
Dale. dale.
Whatchu gonna do?
Cocaine's an anesthetic.
Is that better?
Yeah.
The pain's all gone.
You kidding me?
All I'm saying
is the car is yours.
You're kidding me.
It's in mint condition. brand-new.
It just comes with a slight hitch.
"Slight hitch"?
And he's in there right now?
This... ice cream cake boy?
Karvel. yeah.
And you bring this bullshit to my house?
To my driveway?
It's only 'cause we know
the astute kind of businessman you are
And you appreciate a cool-ass deal.
Why is he fucking talking to me?
I'm disappointed. This is pea-brained.
What you think. I got some kind
of barter system set up here?
And bringing me your enemies?
What? So I gotta deal with them?
Nah. More like an offering.
Yeah. maybe try out some other
bulletproof vests on him...
Enough. Get out of my sight with this.
And get me my money. Otherwise...
Baby?
When we gonna finish our game?
These are my children. Say hi. children.
- 'Sup?
- Hey.
I have adopted them. I'm
raising them up to be men.
I'll be a second.
Okay.
It's a project I've
been working on. so...
Be gone. children.
Wait.
- Man. this some bullshit.
- Just be patient.
Be patient? I've been patient
like a goose. motherfucker.
How is a goose patient?
- You know what I mean.
- What?
The Mojave Desert is my
burial spot of choice.
I suggest you dig deep so
that the coyotes don't get him.
Hola.
¿Cómo estan todos?
¿Cuánto se demora en
llegar la coca de Juliaca?
Um...
¿Cada cuánto llega la coca?
De Sivia hasta aquí son 17 horas.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry. sorry. Uh. uh...
Lento. por favor.
Pero convertir las hojas de
coca en HCL toma cuatro días.
¿Y si quiero más? ¿Más rápido?
Es posible. Pero necesitaría
una o dos ayudantes más.
Creo que podría ayudar con eso. señora.
She likes you. She doesn't like anyone.
I gotta show you something.
American baseball big in my town.
Red Sox my favorite.
Mm. Kansas City for me.
The Royals suck ass.
Come on.
So you're CIA. right?
You. uh. you know about the CIA?
I know you help us.
Fuck the commies. right?
That's right.
You go to other camps. too?
No. not... not yet.
But you might?
You know. I don't know.
And you will bring them
guns and stuff. too?
- Ah.
- Hey!
- Nos vamos a comer ese mono mañana.
- La puta de tu madre.
I hate them! Always same dumb joke.
- What town?
- What?
You said. uh. baseball
was big in your town.
- What town are you from?
- Jinotega. San José De Bocay.
So how'd you come here?
My dad died. Then I came.
What happened to him?
You're no fucking fun. man.
Hey. let's roll his ass
off a cliff and split. man.
- What?
- Let the wolves eat his ass.
Just leave his body out in the open?
That's the dumbest thing I ever heard.
Don't hear you offering
up anything better.
Oh. hell. no!
- Shit.
- Aw. shit. man!
This is not happening.
This my trunk?! Let
me the fuck up outta here!
He sounds really mad right now.
Gotta pull over and deal
with this shit. man.
Nah. we're not far enough out.
How far we gotta be?!
Shit. Get me the fuck up outta here!
Shit.
Shit!
You're gonna need some antibiotics.
It's gonna get infected.
What's wrong?
Nada. Thinking about my gym.
not a wrestling gym. no más.
My boxing gym. too.
And in two months. como dijiste.
- Where's Pedro?
- I'll paint the floor red.
It'll be purita quality.
All-steel frame. corner cushions.
ring padding. ring skirts.
Pedro!
Pedro. what did you do?
I shot a rat.
Why?
It was coming at me.
That's not a rat.
Fuck you. it's not a rat. Look at it.
This is un possum. pendejo.
Possums are nocturnal.
Who gives a shit what it is?
We have a house full of coke
and a body in your trunk.
What if somebody calls the cops?
You got his blood on you.
Go change.
Why?
Just gonna get all dirty again.
Oso.
Can you... Can you put it in the trunk?
We'll bury it with Enrique.
You have a bag?
- Let me up outta here!
- Shit.
Yeah. yeah. Crank it. crank it.
Hey. listen.
Did he pass out?
Oh. shit! Oh. shit! He's got a crowbar!
Give me the gun! Give me
the gun! Give me the gun!
Hurry up! Give me that shit!
- Ow!
- Fuck!
Did you get him?
Shit!
I'm fucking driving. man! Shit!
Shoot!
Aah!
Shit.
I ain't jumpin' down that.
Coke's ready.
Help me load the Jeep.
Hey.
We need a better way.
What?
Transporting the coca
leaves from Colombia or Peru
or wherever the fuck.
Processing it here
doesn't make any sense.
We should be synthesizing
it where it's grown
and transporting it after.
Means dealing with Colombians.
Trying to avoid that.
What's that?
Oh. just give me a minute. will you?
I saw the kid come out of
this tree when I first arrived.
I climbed up there
later. and I found this.
It's called a firefly.
an infrared transmitter.
Anybody with a receiver can locate it.
And thus the camp.
Someone in a helicopter. say.
The only reason they
haven't attacked yet
is he didn't attach
the battery properly.
I can't believe I didn't see this.
Sandinistas are smart.
using a kid. But...
No. no. no.
He asked a lot of questions.
And he knew about the
CIA. And he was from Bocay.
But. uh. mostly I can tell
when someone's lying to me.
Give it to me.
We put it in a tree 5 miles east.
When the helicopters come.
we'll shoot them down.
Lo confesó todo.
Trabaja con el FSLN.
He could be useful. You
could turn him into a double.
- Can't risk it.
- He's just a kid.
A kid who tried to kill us all.
You've seen people die before.
Max.
Enrique.
One other.
¿Y tú?
You've seen someone die before?
Hmm?
Nunca.
Fuck! Fuck!
9-1-1. My dad. I gotta go.
Give me your
keys. I can't take my car.
There's all this shit
in the trunk. Come on.
- You're not right. ese.
- Ramiro pages him. he has to go.
He's suspicious if he doesn't.
Yeah. Hand over your
keys. you fucking oaf.
Gustavo. dame un segundo con él.
I know what happened.
- The fuck you talkin' about?
- In Enrique's kitchen.
When Gustavo was knocked out.
and that fucking
animal was on top of me.
with his hands around my
neck. choking me to death.
And you just stood there
with that fucking knife. staring.
- You don't know what you're saying.
- You froze!
If Gustavo hadn't woken
up. Pedro. I'd be dead.
You know it. and I know it.
Before you go to your
father's. you have to go home
and put on your own clothes first.
And once you're there.
keep your head up.
Just like that. And look him in the eye.
Speak normally.
Be calm.
Say it.
I have to go home first.
put on my own clothes.
keep my head up. look him in the eye.
Be normal.
You fuck this up. and
I'm gonna kill you.
Gustavo!
Dame tus llaves.
Come back after it's done.
How the hell this
motherfucker still alive?
I don't know. Maybe he zombified.
You stupid. You stupid.
Yeah. you know he like an animal.
Can't see no more blood.
- Where'd it go?
- Nigga. I don't know.
What am I. a fucking Navajo?
Shit!
Hey. Saint.
Found a trail.
Please...
Lucia...
No salgas del cuarto.
¿Me entiendes?
You should sleep.
You telling me what to do?
No.
'Cause. you know...
Technically. I'm your boss.
Sorry. patrona.
I'm just kidding.
I just saw you...
crush a man's skull
with your bare hands.
I think that boss/employee relationship
flew out the window.
What's going on with that?
I don't know.
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
No.
Todo va a estar bien.
How did it go?
Arturo went to Enrique's house.
three hours after we'd left.
Fuck.
That was close. We
could've still been there.
Yeah. but it worked.
Ramiro thinks Enrique ran
off after stealing the money.
Good.
Come on. It's time. Let's go.
I heard you wanted to let the kid go.
Do you know how much
damage that would've done?
We're not flying into Hawthorne.
What?
Didn't have time to
vet the customs guys.
Where we gonna land. then?
I'll come back in 10 to pick you up.
Go. Get
the fuck out of here.
In a few weeks. you should
start receiving shipments.
Supplies and weapons
and whatever you need.
Give this to Alejandro.
Tell him. "Don't forget."
Y'all had an animal back there?
Uh. yeah.
I'll give you $23K.
Twenty-th... I bought it
yesterday. It's brand-new.
And the custom rims.
Maybe.
But you sure can fuck up an
upholstery job in 24 hours.
All right. man. One sec.
Let me confer with
my business associate.
You the one went to that fancy school.
but my math tell me. that ain't
enough to pay that Israeli.
Mm.
I got something else I could sell.
You are full of surprises.
Scraggly-ass kid
with a Caddy and a crotch rocket.
Hey. can I have this?
A'ight.
I'll take it.
I'll give you $800.
A kid like you gonna do
with all that money anyway?
Now we re-up.
Listen. uh. thanks for me. you know...
Hey. don't worry 'bout it.
Hey. where you goin'?
Saint!
Hit me tomorrow.
You should invest in your own shovel
if you're in it for the long haul.
And always keep plenty
of heavy duty garbage bags
in the trunk of your car.
And rubber gloves.
Rubbing alcohol.
Air freshener.
Yo. Muir.
Huh?
Set the kid up with 3 more kilos.
Uh. actually. I'm... I'm good.
What?
I'm out.
Thank you.
Well...
You lasted longer than
I thought you would. kid.
This isn't for everybody.
Hey. girl.
Why don't you get out of the pool
and bring your tight ass over here?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm